wonderwebware.com 2017-06-06

# privacy

home >> privacy

_(This is our "Privacy Policy" page. For legal info, clickhere) _

## Privacy Policy for WonderWebWare.com

At wonderwebware.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit wonderwebware.com, and how we safeguard your information.  We never sell your personal information to third parties.

### **Personal Information**

We do not collect personal information. The server collects statistical data as every server - IP, OS type, Browser type, language etc. We use the server statistics only for statistical purposes. If you purchase our product(s) or service(s) - we will use your personal information only for communication purposes.

### **Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.  The information in the log files include  your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

### **Personal information / credit card security**

We don't sell directly, so - we will never see your credit card info. The payment process is secured by the payment service provider.

We use your contact info only for communication between us (as provider/publisher) and you (as customer/client). 

### **Email security**

We do not send unsolicited email. We only write you if you write us. We do not collect email addresses. There are 2 possible situations we can have your email address - if you are our customer and/or if you contact us providing your email address. If you purchase our products or services, we will use the email address provided in the purchase process for sending you important nnotes about updates, upgrades and bugfixes. If you give us your email address when asking question - we will use this email to answer you. We never give your email address to third party. 

_Neither wonderwebware.com nor its owner is responsible for spamming caused by malicious mischief, virus programs, or other form of malicious intent, nor by computer error, ISP error, server error, web host error, nor any unintentional act resulting in unsolicited email. Neither wonderwebware.com nor its owner is responsible for breach of privacy caused by malicious mischief, virus programs, or other form of malicious intent, nor by computer error, ISP error, server error, web host error, nor any unintentional act resulting in divulgence.   All steps are taken to ensure the privacy of all parties who provide wonderwebware.com or its author with personal information, including the storage of email content and addresses on floppy disc or separate hard drive storage_

### Cookies and Web Beacons

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

A cookie is a small piece of information that is sent to your browser when you access a site. 

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.  This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on wonderwebware.com to support our site.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.  However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.  This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
